storeya.com 2018-12-13

# Privacy Statement - StoreYa

StoreYa Feed LTD. ("StoreYa") takes the issue of protecting your privacy very seriously and is well aware that you are concerned about the way in which collected personal information is used and shared. We appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice (namely, this "Privacy Policy") describes how we may collect personal information about you, how we may use it, what choices you have regarding it, and how we protect it. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is a part of the Terms of Use of this StoreYa Web site (Facebook App or the "Site") and we encourage you to become familiar with the terms and conditions contained herein. By accessing and using this Site and the StoreYa Service, you agree that you have read and agree to this Privacy Policy, and that you accept and consent to the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#####  What Information Do We Collect? 

StoreYa may collect various types of information from or about you. During the Site registration process you supply us with basic contact information (such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and company name) that we use for billing and contact purposes. This information is generally entered into fields in the registration forms. Should you purchase any StoreYa Services on or through the Site, the information that you supplied during the registration process, may be used to track details about that purchase. StoreYa may use anonymous, aggregated data to evaluate the effectiveness of its technology. StoreYa is not responsible for any data collected by Organizations using other third-party technology to complete the ordering process. 

#####  The EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “GDPR”) 

StoreYa complies with the GDPR. Any information gathered receives double opt-in consent and can be fully removed from StoreYa’s database upon request. 

##### How Do We Use The Information That We Collect?

StoreYa uses the information that it collects for the following purposes: to fulfill your requests for services, to contact you, for billing purposes, to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal processes or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, for violations of StoreYa's terms of use or as otherwise required by law, to improve the services that StoreYa makes available on the Site, to notify you of changes made to the Site or new products and services made available on or through the Site, to evaluate your needs and customize Site content delivered to you according to those needs, to facilitate the processing of any purchases you make through the Site, to send you promotional material from StoreYa and some of our affiliates, and for other legitimate and lawful business purposes of StoreYa. StoreYa does not share information collected about you with third parties. It is our policy not to sell lists containing personal information about Site users, registrants or subscribers. 

##### How Do We Protect Information Collected About You?

StoreYa places a high value on protecting your personal information. StoreYa takes commercially reasonable measures to protect your personal information. Please be aware that despite using commercially reasonably measures, no security system is impenetrable. If you use a password on our Site, you are responsible for keeping it confidential. Do not share it with any other person. If you believe your password has been misused, please contact us immediately. 

##### Choices About the Use of Your Information.

You may choose to remove the Application from your Facebook account by clicking on "Settings" at the top of your page and selecting Apps in the left column. Click the "x" next to the StoreYa Application's name, then click "remove" to confirm the deletion. In addition, you can delete the shop tab from your Facebook page; however, this will only remove the tab from your Facebook page and your application will remain active until you remove it from your Application Settings area on Facebook. 

##### Linked Sites

For your convenience, some hyperlinks may be posted on the Site that link to other web sites not under the control of StoreYa. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites, nor does this Privacy Policy apply to them. We encourage you to seek out and read the privacy policy of any web site that you visit. In addition, when you initiate a transaction on a web site that our Site links to, even if you reached that site through our Site, the information that you submit to complete that transaction becomes subject to the privacy practices of the owner of that linked site. You should read their privacy policies to understand how they use and protect any personal information they collect. StoreYa is not responsible for the privacy or information practices of its suppliers or any third party Web sites.

##### Changes to Privacy Policy

From time to time, StoreYa may change its privacy practices due to changes in relevant and applicable legal or regulatory requirements, the business or business practices of StoreYa, as part of its ongoing efforts to better serve your needs, or for any other reason which StoreYa in its sole discretion may deem necessary. We encourage you to review this Policy whenever you visit our Site or use our Service to view the current Privacy Policy. 

##### Who Can You Contact For More Information?

If you wish to contact StoreYa about privacy related issues, you may do so by sending an email to: Legal@StoreYa.com
